promodirect.com 2013-08-10

# Promo Direct Privacy Statement

Blog & Connect

Connect with us and get marketing tips to enhance and build your brand.

Customer Testimonials

"Thank you for assisting me with our promotional product needs at our latest event for Nickelodeon and Nick at Night. The products we ordered with your company were exceptional in quality." -Candace Bell, MTV

"Everyone was really friendly and seemed to have the same sense of urgency in getting my items to me in the time frame I required." -Lisa Huff, Select Media Services

"With the help of your best sellers, we have been able to market to our customers better. Sincere thanks to Promo Direct." -Thomas Wright, Wright Financial

Home » Promo Direct Privacy Statement

##  Promo Direct Privacy Statement

Promo Direct has created this privacy statement to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy. This policy describes our practices regarding personal information collected through our website or through any other means. We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy from time to time; the effective date noted below will indicate the date the policy was last updated. Please visit our website periodically to review any changes. 

## What Happens to the information we collect from you?

All information you provide will be kept confidential and is used to support our business relationship and the service we provide. This website uses an order inquiry form to allow you to request information, products and services. We collect your contact information (such as your e-mail address or your company information) to allow us to send samples, orders, information about our products, and promotional materials. Your contact information is also used to get in touch with you when necessary. You may opt-out of receiving future communication. Just send an email to info@promodirect.com to make this request. 

## Personal Information Disclosure

Promo Direct will not give or sell any information you provided to any third parties under any circumstances for its use in marketing or solicitation without your consent. The information protected includes any information about you, your order, and your purchase history. Your information may be shared with contractors of Promo Direct for the purpose of performing services for Promo Direct related only to your order or sample request. Promo Direct may release personal identifiable information when required to by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a legal process. 

## Choice/Opt-Out

When you opt-in to receive communications from Promo Direct, you will receive information we believe will be of use and interest to you. For example: 

  * We keep you informed about the latest deals, new service, sell-out specials, etc. that we think you will find valuable. 
  * We may update you on any important changes to our website.

If you choose to opt out of our communication, you may do so in the following ways: 

You may e-mail your request to: info@promodirect.com

You may send mail to the following postal address: 

Promo Direct

931 American Pacific Dr. # 100 

Henderson, NV 89014

You may fax in your request to : **800-748-3326**

You may call to make your request at : **800-748-6150 (Toll Free)**

Privacy Policy Last Modified September 30th, 2011
